Alec Gall

Jeannette, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Alec-Gall/ce71cceb524dc628

Developed websites and Apps as both the sole developer and as part of a team of developers. Extensive experience utilizing Drupal, HTML 5, and Bootstrap along with Craft, WordPress, JavaScript, and JQuery. An effective project manager with client communication experience. Additionally, has worked in manufacturing environments understanding product development, production, and warehousing. Consistent reviews show a creative, self-directed, goal oriented, and solid performer. Repeatedly exhibits the willingness, adaptability, and capability to accept new challenges and develop new skills.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

SAP Project Synergy Intern

Westinghouse Electric - Cranberry, PA - May 2016 to August 2016

- Supported HTML/Java development for an internal mobile reporting system
- Participated in analysis discussions with managers and consultants for implementation of ITSM ChaRM
- Created SAP Lumira financial reports for managers and directors that actively update when new data is entered into the system
- Conducted testing of new vs old systems for the SAP HANA implementation

Lead Web Developer

Developed websites for the Multicultural Resource Center - Erie, PA - May 2015 to December 2015

Lake Erie Region Conservancy, and Mothers Against Teen Violence.

Web Co-Developer

Supported team development of websites for Lucy's First Steps, Walking in Black History, and UPMC.

Project Manager

UPMC Hamot App - Web app for UPMC staff to receive news updates via smart phone to replace their e-mail newsletter system.

- Experience in multiple content management systems, including Drupal, WordPress, and Craft
- Created content from the ground up using HTML 5, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and JQuery
- Conducted requirements gathering sessions, milestone reviews, and wrap-up meetings with clients
- Created user guides and conducted training sessions for clients

Server Admin

• Responsible for initial creation and maintenance of website files and databases on the company server

Database Entry

Carclo Technical Plastics - Latrobe, PA - December 2014 to January 2015

- Performed data entry for 3 medical manufacturing cells in Q-Pulse, a Quality System Database
- · Created records for work instructions, setting cards, forms, drawings, and specifications
- Edited work instructions for medical products
- Conducted a gap analysis of Q-Pulse documentation records against actual active products

Quality Engineering Inspector

Carclo Technical Plastics - May 2014 to August 2014

Programmed and ran Coordinate Measuring Machines (CMMs)

- Performed measurements with height stands and calipers
- Interpreted 2D component drawings and supplemental specifications
- Collected and reported metrology data
- Performed statistical analysis supporting validations on manufacturing processes for medical devices
- Assembled LED based optics for aircraft safety lights.

Computer Sales Associate

Best Buy - Greensburg, PA - April 2012 to February 2013

- Greet and assist customers with their computing needs
- Provide technical knowledge on use and compatibility of computer products
- Upselling computer accessories and warranties
- Performed final sale at the register
- Updated customer database

EDUCATION

B.S. in Management Information Systems

Pennsylvania State University - Erie, PA May 2017